{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622669","name":"Fantasy Island","address":"7059 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Vincent Spica","licenseNumber":"246032","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.13200,42.33089","geojson":{"id":"51622669","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.132000533,42.330887269]},"properties":{"name":"Fantasy Island","owner":"Vincent Spica","address":"7059 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"246032","establishmentid":"51622669","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"6/21/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"715","name":"Yacht Club Exclusive","address":"7059 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"1013","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #302","address":"7060 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"716","name":"Jordans Family Restaurant","address":"7031 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"2073","name":"Senor Lopez Taqueria Mexican","address":"7146 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"515","name":"Holy Cross Council 2739","address":"4381 Larkins St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3914","name":"Subway #29822","address":"7300 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"743","name":"Freer Bar","address":"7355 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"4094","name":"Corner Pocket Lounge","address":"7304 StJohn St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"5348","name":"Hard Bodies Bar","address":"7443 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3288","name":"Los Dos Amigos-1","address":"7115 Parkwood St","zipcode":"4821"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50161","inspectionDate":"2019-12-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.6149","violationDescription":"Definitions; satisfaction of  section 3-603.11 of food code; statement; disclosures and reminders; text;  exemptions.*  Sec. 6149. (1) As used in this section: (P)    (a) &quot; Publicly available&quot; means  accessible to consumers, without their having to request it, before their  placing food orders or making their selections.    (b) &quot; Selection information&quot; means  whatever consumers read to make their order selections, such as menu, table  tent, placard, chalkboard, or other written means.    (2) To satisfy section 3-603.11 of the food code, the food establishment may  provide the following statement on selection information so that it is publicly  available: &quot; Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or  served raw. Consuming raw or undercooked meats, poultry, seafood, shellfish, or  eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness&quot;.(P)    (4) The language for the menu items shall match the language used for the  disclosure and the reminder.Â  The  disclosure and reminder may also be in additional languages.(P)    (5) The text for disclosures and reminders shall meet the following requirements: (P)    (a) The text size for statements on handheld  menus or table tents shall be visually equivalent to at least 11-point font  size or may be visually equivalent to the font size of menu item descriptions.    (b) Text color provides a clear contrast to  background.    (6) Table tents, placards, or chalkboards that are used exclusively to list food  items that are offered as daily, weekly, or temporary specials are exempt from  the requirements of this section when those food items also appear in the  primary selection information that contains the disclosures and reminders  meeting the requirements of this section.(S)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Menu","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-03-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not approved for use","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Sanitizer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use.  Provide approved source."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-01-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (prep)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.6141","violationDescription":"Sec. 6141. (1) A food service establishment in which solid foods are sold and consumed on the premises shall prominently display a poster in the kitchen area of the food service establishment diagramming and explaining the antichoking techniques safe for both adults and children approved by the department for dislodging foreign obstacles caught in the throat of a choking person.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"49762","inspectionDate":"2019-11-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622669"}}